I love ice cream, but 1,000 calories a
pint is just not going to help me reach
my goal. So instead, I've been making
low calorie, high protein ice creams in
my Ninja Creamy that I could eat every
night and still lose weight and build
muscle. Here are the five I made this
week. Biscoff protein ice cream, which
was a cinnamon base with Biscoff cookies
mixed in throughout. Then I made a M&M
McFlurry, which you know, the one from
McDonald's is so good. So I decided to
recreate that. Then I made a Rocky Road.
This one was so good. Rocky Road is such
a slept on ice cream flavor. So, this
was a chocolate base with mini
marshmallows, almonds, and chocolate
chips. Then, I made a Thai tea ice
cream. This was so good. This is might
be my favorite recipe I've ever made.
It's a Thai tea base with sweetened
condensed milk basically dripping down
the sides. And last but not least, I
made a double Oreo. This was a black
cocoa base, so the base that the Oreo
cookies are. And I mixed in some mini
Oreos throughout.